You
Oh
Is that all you've got fan out I struck her not
Dammit
I'm coming
Regroup otherwise they'll pick us off one by one
Come on idiot let's go
Geku in
How can you you?
Welcome back
Let's go we're not leaving him here
Stop it
What the hell are you doing?
Follow your orders
Retreat
Okay
I think that's enough out of you
Hey wait you're that weird kid from Shinjuku the one who freaked out and almost killed a bunch of our troops
Please my lord may I have permission to kill him?
No
Afraid not
Huh?
But look at him he's asking for it
I know but I'm betting that Lord Farid will want the kid alive
Keep me covered guys I'm going back in
Don't you dare
Why not?
We have to get out of here
What like hell we are?
Let me go
Someone stop him
That's a direct order
Damn
They've got backup inbound
Come on guys
It's time
No Shinoa
Tell me you're joking
They've captured Goren
He's part of our family remember?
What would you have us do now?
We're clothing
Hmm let's see
There it'll probably reward us if we can't
It's time
Damn
They've got backup inbound
Come on guys
It's time
No Shinoa
Tell me you're joking
They've captured Goren
He's part of our family remember?
What would you have us do now?
We're clothing
Hmm let's see
There it'll probably reward us if we capture them and keep them alive
Besides it's no fun if we just let them go free
I won't leave him
Damn it
That's not how we
We're retreating right now
That's an order
Move
I won't leave him
Dammit
That's not how we
We're retreating right now
That's an order
Move
I won't leave him
Damn it
That's not how we
We're retreating right now
Stop now! That's an order! Move!
Oh, I love playing chase.
What's this? It's hot!
It must be magic.
Illusionary spell. One strong enough that it's managed to affect a noble's brain.
Humans shouldn't be able to control spells as powerful as this one.
So then, I wonder who's teaching you all these new magic tricks.
Ah, and there's more of you, I see.
Bastard! Dad!
What do you think you're doing? Get out of here now!
Not without you!
We won't leave you behind!
I'm as good as Dad.
Retreat thought I told you to shut up!
Gerhen!
Stay back!
It'll slaughter every one of you.
Leave them, Goshi.
Sir, I can't!
Complete the move!
Leave him, Pin Бог!
He's killing him!
Blast it!
Aye!
A-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-the-e-a-ag-e-a-a-a-a-a-a-a!
Super impressive, Lord Crowley.
Now is not the time to start fawning over him, Chess.
Your friends have left you behind.
I guess they don't like me very much.
It seemed like quite the opposite if you ask me.
Either way, you're mine now.
Get him bound nice and tight while we wait for Farid.
Yes, sir.
I'm sorry, Lieutenant General Coretto.
But I'm afraid the test subject won't be ready for transport until 1700 hours.
We need it sooner.
Do whatever it takes to have the subject ready by 1600 hours.
If we screw this up, the human race is extinct.
Sir!
Hey, Kurato!
Brother Seishiro, what are you doing here?
Father wanted me to come by and say hello.
So he wants you to keep tabs on me.
I'm surprised he didn't send you earlier.
If our intel's correct, the nobles are going to attack soon.
You sure you're going to be able to handle that kind of fight by yourself?
Father won't tolerate any screw-ups.
They'll be hell to pay if you lose.
Do you think I'm worried about him?
Hey, take this seriously.
Sorry, but you just sound so ridiculous.
If I fail now, it's over.
Our entire species is dead.
And you still expect me to be afraid of the old man?
Hey, you better watch what you're saying.
If I report your attitude to Father, he might strip you of your...
Cowards who are too scared to fight on the front lines should shut up and stay out of the way.
A coward? You're going to regret that!
Brother, did you just put your hands on me?
Hey, I've got orders for Father to observe you.
He won't let you hurt me.
Father is very resourceful.
But how could he protect you if you were to die right now?
Kirito Hiragi, I'm arresting you for Les Majesté against our father.
I order you to restrain this man!
You're crazy!
Do you honestly think you'll get away with this?
Of course I will.
Well, as long as I succeed at saving the world today.
Lieutenant General, all of our squads will be ready to head out shortly.
I'd recommend leaving in 30 minutes.
Excellent.
Wait, you're leaving? Where do you think you're going?
The vampires are coming to attack us!
The vampires aren't going to step foot in Kanto.
We're stopping them in Nagoya.
You bastard!
I dispatched the Shibuya troops because you said you could hold off our enemies in Shinjuku!
Kirito, what have you been doing behind Father's back?
Do you really think you could disobey the leader of the demon army and live?
You can't be that stupid!
You're lucky, Seishiro.
You're a real pain in the ass, but you're always loyal to authority.
You'll make a good servant later.
But for the time being, you'll be locked up.
I'll use you when I return.
Hey, let me go already!
Dammit, you can't just drag me around everywhere!
I can't believe you guys.
You're really just going to leave Gurren behind to die?
Hey, Shinoa.
Yes?
He's your team member.
It's your job to shut him up.
You listen.
If we all go back, we might be able to save him.
I'm sorry.
But we made a promise before the mission started.
You agreed that when the time came to retreat, you'd leave no matter what.
Yeah.
But still...
Look at the Major General.
He's known the Lieutenant Colonel longer than you have, but he understands our duty.
You see?
So, we're just gonna...
It's not that we're abandoning him.
We're actually honoring his orders.
Remember, the point of the mission wasn't to come back alive.
The goal was...
Victory.
I know.
We still have work to do.
And people to protect.
If Gurren were here, he'd tell you to complete your mission.
You're right.
Major General Shinya.
Goshi.
Your quick thinking saved us back there.
Is everybody else all right?
Yeah.
In a manner of speaking.
There's no time for regret.
We have to move.
Tell us what your orders are.
All right.
Let's find Narumi's team.
They should have saved all the hostages by now.
It's likely that they'll be waiting for us at the rendezvous point.
You want us to ditch Gurren and put the mission first.
Like he doesn't matter.
Like you don't care what happens to him.
I care.
We can't give up.
We're living in a messed up world.
If we don't protect our family, then why bother living at all?
Why try to save it if we're just going to abandon the people we care about?
Gurren is...
His family.
He saved me.
I heard you were screaming in your sleep again.
What kind of nightmare was it this time?
The same as always.
I had to watch a vampire kill everyone I cared about.
And you wet the bed again, didn't you, kid?
I'm not a baby.
I've never wet the bed.
It was just a dream.
Go back to sleep.
You're starting to be a real pain.
What do you know?
Why don't I hang out in here until you fall asleep again?
Would you like that?
Not really.
Hey, Gurren.
Shut up and go to sleep.
I'm reading here.
I've been trying to figure out why you saved me.
I don't have a family anymore.
I've never really had one.
Not since I was born.
My parents tried to kill me.
And then when I finally found a new family, I lost them too.
Maybe I'm cursed.
I don't know why I'm alive.
Or if I'm even worth it.
Do you find life to be painful?
I don't know.
It hurts so much.
It hurts so much, Gurren.
Then you and I are the same.
A long time ago, I couldn't save someone important to me.
But I'm still here.
You're still alive and miserable.
That's life.
It's full of things you can't escape.
You have to eat, crap, sleep, remember when you'd rather forget.
The thing is, one day you might be able to keep someone else from hurting the way you do.
You can help them.
So you just have to endure and wait for that day to come.
Until then.
Whenever life feels like it's too painful to go on, just concentrate on killing vampires.
That'll help give you some focus, at least.
Yeah, okay.
I suppose I can do that.
All you have to do is survive, you.
Until that moment you find something that makes life worth living again.
One day you'll feel better.
I promise.
You'll help someone else and realize all this pain was worth it.
Gurren.
How will I know?
What if I miss the person I'm supposed to help?
I'm sure you'll know.
Now go to sleep.
You've got training tomorrow.
Okay.
I guess I just can't get this teamwork thing down.
Sorry.
But I'm going back for Gurren.
Put those down right now!
If you take another one!
If I can't save my family...
No!
Don't do it!
You idiot!
Then life's not worth living.
No, stop it!
You've already taken two pills today!
Spit them out, you!
You'll die!
Hey, what are you doing?
It's not such a big deal.
I actually feel kind of great,
so maybe that means I'm not...
No, don't do this.
You fool!
Take the girls and go find Narumi's team.
We'll join you guys later.
Sir, this is gonna be ugly.
Get out of the way!
You!
Stay with us!
No.
No way.
You!
No!
So the humans attacked Lord Crowley's territory as well.
I'm kind of thirsty.
We should get him there and see if they left anyone alive.
No, I'm afraid this is as far as any of you will go.
What are you talking about?
Oh, traitor!
Now then, where are you, my friend?
Wait, this is...
It's some kind of joke, right?
What?
Okay.
We'll be right back.
How's the test subject doing?
A little unstable. Seems to be in quite a bit of pain.
Then tell the scientists to increase the dosage. We'll force the thing into submission.
It's possible the subject won't survive another increase.
If we don't stick to the timeline, then we're all dead.
I'll see that it's done.
Hold on. One more thing before you go.
Sir?
Any update from Gurren in Nagoya?
Gurren says that things are fine.
Things are fine.
I'll buy that.
Hurry it up!
The demon company won't be able to stall the vampires very much longer.
The demon company won't fuse.
The demon company won't be able to assemble the Olga's hands.
The demon company needs to beMER
Über the officers Kay Ford
the Capurant
The demon company ust incidents
woman and server
The demon company spends the残 план
with her company to get her
Remember, women are fearful.
Embry her son of a legend
Or夫 would be part of the villain
Not like her, or Alfred this that is whom she sees
ação
Next time on Seraph of the End, Traitorous Allies.